var questions = [{
    "question":"Which antibacterial drug increases the risk of developing serotonin syndrome?",
    "option1":"Trimethoprim",
    "option2":"Vancomycin",
    "option3":"Linezolid",
    "option4":"All of the above",
    "answer":"3"
    }, {
          "question":"Thiazide diuretics act at which point along the nephron?",
           "option1":"Proximal tubule",
             "option2":"Ascending loop of Henle",
             "option3":"Distal convoluted tubule",
             "option4":"Cortical collecting duct",
             "answer":"3"
              }, {
          "question":"Many medicines harmlessly discolor urine. Which of the following drug-urine discoloration combinations is incorrect?",
           "option1":"Nitrofurantoin - Brown",
             "option2":"Amitriptyline - Blue",
             "option3":"Rifampicin - Red",
             "option4":"None of the above",
             "answer":"4"
              }, {
          "question":"Which of the following medicines increases the risk of mercaptopurine and azathioprine toxicity?",
           "option1":"Allopurinol",
             "option2":"Clarithromycin",
             "option3":"Amiloride",
             "option4":"Minocycline",
             "answer":"1"
              }, {
          "question":" Prolonged use of proton-pump inhibitors is linked to what electrolyte disturbance?",
           "option1":"Hyponatremia",
             "option2":"Hypokalemia",
             "option3":"Hypophosphatemia",
             "option4":"Hypomagnesemia",
             "answer":"4"
              }, {
          "question":"Which antibacterial drug class does NOT work by inhibiting protein synthesis?",
           "option1":"Aminoglycosides",
             "option2":"Macrolides",
             "option3":"Fluoroquinolones",
             "option4":"Tetracyclines",
             "answer":"3"
              }, {
          "question":"Which of the following statements is true?",
           "option1":"Protamine sulfate is an ineffective antidote for LMWH toxicity",
             "option2":"LMWHs act less on thrombin than unfractionated heparin",
             "option3":"Lower risk of heparin-induced thrombocytopenia with LMWHs",
             "option4":"All of the above",
             "answer":"4"
              }, {
          "question":"Which antiarrhythmic drug class, as set out in the Vaughan-Williams classification, works chiefly via potassium channel block?",
           "option1":"Class Ib / Ic",
             "option2":"Class II",
             "option3":"Class III",
             "option4":"Class IV",
             "answer":"3"
              }, {
          "question":"Beta-2 agonists stimulate sodium-potassium ATP-ase pumps on cell surface membranes, causing a shift of potassium ions from the extracellular to the intracellular compartment.",
           "option1":"True",
             "option2":"False",
             "answer":"1"
              }, {
          "question":"Second-generation antipsychotics are more associated with metabolic effects – such as weight gain, lipid changes and diabetes mellitus – compared to first-generation antipsychotics.",
           "option1":"True",
             "option2":"False",
             "answer":"1" }
             ]
              